Hey everyone and welcome to this new video. I'm going to tell you a bit about the different materials of clothing I wear.
Shiny stuff, mostly, I think everything. A lot of shiny stuff and latex, PVC, PU leather, all these materials and just check it out.
I'm starting with latex, which is natural caoutchouc. I'm wearing green latex top.
There are different colors in which you can buy OA latex. Mostly you will see black latex. There are different kinds of gorges when it comes to latex. 0.4 thickness or 0.2. So it can be a bit thicker or thinner and it is really elastic.
like I can stretch it a lot. I got to know the material when I saw it at a gothic event
and after that I was really interested because I already knew PVC and other materials and I was
like what's that it's shiny it looks cool so I bought my first dress made of latex it was a
plain black skater dress and after that I also started to make my own latex clothing. I like to
wear them for photo shoots or for clubbing. It always depends on the weather because it's not
isolated so if it's cold outside it's cold when you wear latex and the same when it's hot so
there is like perfect latex temperature of I don't know 26 degree or something.
I'm rambling. Anyway I like the feeling of latex so that's something everyone has to
experience herself or himself because it's a different kind of feeling apart from normal
clothes. You may have seen it on my pictures and I wrote in the caption
matte latex. So what's matte latex? I'm going to reveal the secret of matte latex and
it's simply normal latex but the matte side inside out. Like matte? Shiny. That's the
whole story it's normal latex sheet and you just turn it inside out so you have
a completely different look and a different feel it's slightly velvety and
you have you have the shiny side on the inside that's it up next is datex I
already made a whole video about this material so check it out if you want to
or more I'm just giving the basics here it may look like latex but it's not latex because it's
fabric on the inside as you can see here so on the outside it's natural couch look and on the
inside it's spandex it's not glued together but soon and it's stretchy nevertheless and it really
feels like latex. But it's much easier to put on, it's easy to get out of and you
can just use your shiner to make it more shiny obviously. I own a few datex pieces
it's not going to substitute my latex wardrobe but it's a nice addition to
latex because of the more easy way to put on. This is PVC and PVC is shiny but
it's not latex. I'm mentioning this because when I post pictures on my
Instagram profile wearing PVC a lot of people still comment oh nice latex
outfit but it's not latex. Unlike leather or latex there is no clear definition of
the material PVC. Most shops simply call it PVC to summarize everything that's
shiny and coated fabric. Although if you check the labels you will find that most
of the garments are not made of the exact same materials or ingredients.
There are a lot of items made of PVC like corsets or leggings. There is
colorful PVC as well like this skirt. I own a lot of PVC mostly dresses I think
and skirts and I like to wear them because they're fun to wear, they're shiny
but they're easier to wear than latex because of the fabric and I think they
have a nice look to them and most of the time I do prefer them over latex coming
to PO leather, faux leather, fake leather whatever you may call it as with PVC
there's no clear definition of the material there are different structures
some are more shiny and elastic some are more stiffer like with harnesses or
corsets for me it's like everything that looks kind of like leather but not real
leather like this dress here and it's a bit shiny and I like to combine it with
almost everything with t-shirts as for leggings and I have a lot of PU leather
dresses I like to wear them because they're easy to wear they're easy to put
on and they look good, they shape the figure a bit and I've got several items
of different structures of PU leather. Coming to wet look I think every girl
owns one pair of wet look leggings by now because you can buy them everywhere
wear in every store. It's basically nothing else than coated lycra which you
know as sportswear maybe. So it's really thin, it's not figure shaping but on the
other hand it's really comfortable and you can get it in different colors like
gold or red or classic black and still a bit shiny so I like to wear it every day
because it is comfortable and it's really not a big deal to wear anymore
since it's kind of fashion nowadays. Not real outfit change because coming to
leather in real leather I don't own that many items made of leather because I'm
not really into leather I don't have to buy real leather I'm fine with
four leather I have two or three corsets and some accessories like this choker
But of course you can buy every type of outfit made from leather like dresses and trousers, jackets and stuff like that. It's up to everyone if he or she is into leather. Of course it's not vegan. I'm fine with a few items I own.
So, thanks for watching this video, I hope I could tell you something about all the different
materials and I hope people start recognizing wet look as a wet look and not only say, oh
it's latex because it's shiny.
Anyway, I hope you had fun, if you liked it click on the subscribe button and leave a
comment telling me what's your favorite material.
about... I don't know.
Have fun, bye!